carrier411.com 2019-06-29

# Carrier411 - Privacy Policy

|  |  **Contact Customer Service About Any Questions**

If you have any other questions, please call (888) 411-9661 between 9:00 AM and 6:00 PM EST Monday through Friday.

Carrier411 Services, Inc. understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to our website ("Site") and recognizes our obligation to keep your personal and business information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you, along with the list of carriers your company uses and monitors.

**Last Updated February 15, 2010**

We may modify this Privacy Policy ("Policy") at any time, and accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent.

**Collection of Information**

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, address, phone number, fax number, credit card number, email address or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to subscribe or to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP address (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information without limitation.

**Monitoring List**

One of the many benefits of using Carrier411 is the ability to monitor carriers (and brokers) your company uses, get custom reports about their status, and be alerted to changes in authority, insurance, safety and performance issues. In order to monitor companies with Carrier411, you need to maintain a list through our Site, which we refer to as your Monitoring List ("Monitoring List").

Carrier411 Services, Inc. treats your Monitoring List as highly confidential information. Accordingly, we neither disclose nor release information about your Monitoring List to customers or any other party, unless required by law. Simply put, your Monitoring List is not available for other Carrier411 customers to access or obtain. The only people who can access information about your Monitoring List are the Carrier411 staff of professionals, and your trusted employees who have been granted access (by your company) to use your Carrier411 account. In a related manner, we trust your company will help guard its account by carefully controlling authorized access. Please restrict access to your Carrier411 account by limiting it to trusted company employees. Should any employee who knows your account username and password leave your company for any reason, we highly encourage you to change your account username and password immediately for security reasons.

**Use of Information**

Carrier411 Services, Inc. uses your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your order and administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that may be of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. Carrier411 Services, Inc. may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third-party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other websites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If Carrier411 Services, Inc. is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information may be among the transferred assets.

**Opt-Out Email Advertising**

In the event you do not wish to receive promotional email from Carrier411 Services, Inc. or its business partners, follow the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive.

**Browser Cookies**

When you visit the Site, Carrier411 Services, Inc. or a third-party advertiser may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features.

**Website Links**

The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. Carrier411 Services, Inc. is not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any third party sites.

**Website Security**

We have policies and procedures to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on our secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. Carrier411 Services, Inc. uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet.

**Modifying Personal Information**

If you need to update your Personal Information, please login or call us toll-free at (888) 411-9661.

|   
---|---|---
